■
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0
161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76
l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228
209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
字幕来源：网络收集  后期：L.C.
-来场比赛  -强  有首歌
-One contest -Jon. One song
-相信我  -快他妈踩刹车
-Trust me.-Hit the fucking brakes.
-这地方真不错  -我来拿冲浪板
-This place looks sweet. -I'll get the boards.
-那是我的宝贝  -滚
-That's my boy. -Yeah. Fuck you.
-那人是谁  -从圣克莱拉来的怪胎
-Hey. Who is this guy? -Some freak from Santa Clara.
-别担心他  -别他妈理他
-Don't worry about him. -Who gives a fuck?
不  我不担心这个  就是说说而已
No. I'm not worried about it. I'm just saying.
听着  这他妈是美国  不是他妈津巴布韦
Listen. Man. This is fucking America. Man. Not fucking Zimbabwe.
津巴布韦  他是一加勒比混蛋
Zimbabwe? Yo. Fucking Caribbean. Bitch.
我跟你说过多少次了  给我滚蛋
How many times I gotta remind you? Kiss my ass.
别理那玩意
Yo. Leave this motherfucker here. Man.
我会为戴茜小姐开车  也会载你回家  混蛋
I'll drive Miss Daisy. I'll drive your ass home. Bitch.
我会踩着冲浪板直接开到你
Drive this surfboard right up your
-咱们走  -闯进来了
-Let's go. -We're breaking in!
-低声一点  -闭嘴
-Hey. Keep it down. -Shut up!
-闭嘴  -怎么  你怕了
-Shut up! -Why. Are you scared?
是啊  我怕了
Yeah. Yeah. I'm scared.
别把我冲浪板掉地下  不然弄死你
Don't drop my board or I'll cut your throat.
拿着这个  你这个混蛋
Take this. Aryan bitch.
我不知道你从哪里找着这个  看似纳粹的光头党
I don't know where you found this swastika-waving wannabe skinhead.
-滚远点  -死神经
-Get the fuck away from me. -Fucking psycho.
别动  看他有什么反应
Wait till you see the reaction on his face.
这是乡下  你他妈
Yo. It's corn-fed. Fucking
你们他妈的在我海滩上干什么
What the fuck are you doing on my beach?
你说呢  大惊小怪什么  别这么激动
What you say. Fussy? You're too red-eyed.
你又不管这里  管你的婊子窝去吧
You don't run this thing. You run your pussy-whore blood-clot.
他说你管不着大海
He says that you don't own the ocean.
真的
Is that a fact?
我告诉你们
Let me tell you something.
我拥有从这儿  到灯塔之间的每一滴水
I own every drop of water between here and the lighthouse
每一粒沙  我拥有所有东西
as well as the sand and everything on it.
我想  现在我也拥有你们
Which I guess now includes you.
你知道吗  快他妈滚远
Hey. You know what? Fuck that.
干嘛不给我吹个箫  你这老混蛋
Why don't you just blow me. You old fuck?
冷静点  不管怎么讲  我们也打算走了
Hey. Take it easy. Man. We're done here. Anyway.
咱们才刚刚开始
Uh-uh. We're just getting started.
-耶稣啊  -翻你的门进来  又不是
-Jesus. -We jumped your gate. It's not like
在你家水池里游泳
we went for a swim in your pool.
-我们从不闯进别人家的  -除非人家邀请我们
-We'd never go into anyone's house. -Unless we were invited.
嘿
Hey.
一定要把头割下来
Make sure you take the head.
舔我的老二吧  你这垃圾
Yo. Suck my dick. Bitch.
肖恩  看我的
Hey. Shane. Check this out.
妈的
Ow. Fucking
估计踢到脊椎了
I think I hit the spine.
狗娘养的
Oh. You son of a bitch.
你这垃圾
You fucking
清理干净
Clear the shot.
玩儿完了吧  再唧唧歪歪啊  贱人
There you go. You ain't talking shit now. You bitch.
捉鬼小精灵2
还不坏  是吧
Not bad. Right?
不坏  不坏
Not bad. Not bad.
真的不错
Not bad at all.
对吧  小妹
Right. Little sister?
谢谢你
Thank you.
-告诉你这儿很好的  -是吗  太阳呢
-Told you this was gonna work out. -Yeah? Then where's the sun?
太阳这牛皮算我吹破了
The sun's overrated.
笑一个嘛
Gives you wrinkles.
-克里斯  -来吧
-Chris. -Come on.
放手
Get out.
-友好一点嘛  -我向来很友好
-Be nice. -I'm always nice.
是你脾气不好
You're the one with the temper.
你看  这就是不友好
Now. See? That wasn't nice.
-你真混蛋  -是啊
-You're such an ass. -Yup.
来了
Coming.
-上帝啊  你看你  -嘿  吉丽安阿姨
-Oh. My goodness. Iook at you. -Hi. Hey. Aunt Jillian.
没想到你们会来  这次真早
I wasn't expecting you for ages. You're so early.
对不起  我们不知道多久才能到这儿
We didn't know how long it would take.
上次我见你  你才这么高
The last time I saw you. You were this high.
-那时我还喝奶呢  -过来
-I drank my milk. -Come here.
你长大了  你这个小
You drank your milk. You silly
妮可  过来  过来
And Nicole. Come here. Come here.
让我看看你
Let me look at you.
真漂亮  你
You're so beautiful. You
真像你妈妈
You look so much like your mom.
-我真是太伤心了  -谢谢
-It's totally blowing my mind. -Thanks.
对不起
I'm sorry.
太抱歉了  我不
I'm so sorry that I didn't
-没事  吉丽安阿姨  -不知道
-That's okay. Aunt Jillian. -Didn't know
吉丽安阿姨
Aunt Jillian.
-谢谢  -你看我
-Thank you. -Look at me.
先把你们安顿下来吧
Let's get you guys situated.
这所房子就像生意场中的所说的  "尚未雕琢的钻石"
So this is what we call in the business "a diamond in the rough."
它骨架很好  就是需要略微装修一下
It's got great bones. But it could use a little sprucing up.
进来
There we go.
这是厨房  那边有储藏室
So there's the kitchen over there and some storage over there.
这是睡房  起居室  到这儿来
Sleeping space here. Living Come this way.
洗浴室
Half-bath through there
情调很好哦  风水很不错的
and it creates a very nice rustic-y charm. Feng-shui-type flow
然后从这出来  快来
that leads us straight out to Come on.
从这里出来
This out to here.
就是这了  啦啦啦
There we go. Ta-da!
很漂亮
Beautiful.
注意台阶
Just watch that step there.
空气很新鲜
So lots of fresh air
嘿  嘿
Scat. Scat.
无视那个老头好了
Just ignore the old guy.
一个月650美元  你们觉得行吗
I was thinking 650 a month. How does that sound?
Six-fifty?
我知道  至少该要800美元一月  但我能怎么办呢
I know. I know. I could be getting at least 800. but what am I gonna do?
问你们要全价  你们是我的家人
Charge you guys full price? You're family.
行
Well. It sounds good.
你俩来这儿真是太好了
It is so great having you both here.
这是钥匙  记住  J是我吉丽安的缩写
Here's the keys. Remember. Jillian with a J.
我还以为她会免费让我们住这儿
-I thought she was gonna let us stay here for free.
我也这么想
Well. Yeah. So did I.
-这能用吗  -我觉得应该没问题
-Does this even work? -Yeah. I'm sure it's fine.
-接上电  掸掉灰  -不能用
-Plug it in. Dust it off. -It doesn't work.
妮可  你看这个
Hey. Nicole. Check this out.
上帝啊
Oh. My God.
把这东西放好  它得立起来
We're gonna put this up right now. These have got to go up.
搞不好碰上就受伤了
It's a safety hazard.
-挂在那个钉子上  那个  -等等  这儿
-Right there on that nail. Right there. -Oh. Oh. Wait. There?
这地方现在什么都有了
Now this place has everything.
克里斯  咱们在哪里睡
Chris. Where are we gonna sleep?
不  不  后面有卧室  还有蒲团
No. No. No. There's a bedroom back here. And we have that futon.
最好再找一个用过的蒲团  放在那边
Maybe we can pick up another futon. Used. For right over there.
-蒲团  用过的蒲团  -是啊
-A futon? A used futon? -Yeah.
好的  行啊
Great. Yeah.
我觉得这像大学宿舍  只是一点不酷
You know. I bet this is just like college. Only not cool.
你知道吗
You know what?
咱们先出去一会  好吗
Maybe we'll get out of here for a little bit. Okay?
一会再整理行李  好吗
We can unpack later. Let's go.
好
Okay.
就在这儿
It's right here.
请问现在几点了
Hey. You wouldn't happen to have the time?
呃
Um Uh
事实上你戴着表  所以
You're actually wearing a watch. So
是
Yeah.
已经坏了
Yeah. I'm pretty sure it's broken. You know.
哦
Oh. Uh-huh.
你是克里斯·爱梅森  对吧
You're Chris Emerson. Right?
对对  你叫什么  哥们
Yeah. Yeah. What's your name. Man?
-阿历克斯  -嘿
-Alex. -Hey.
你被这次巡回赛淘汰真是太糟了
Dude. It's too bad you got kicked off the circuit.
你是自斯莱特和帕沃斯以来  最了不起的冲浪手
You were the most amazing surfer since Slater. Since Powers. Man.
-你完全把那些家伙整惨了  -谢谢  哥们  非常感谢
-You totally screwed that guy up. -Thanks. Dude. I appreciate that.
你一个人在这儿干什么
So. What are you doing here alone?
有点怪异  是吧
That sounded kind of creepy. Didn't it?
有点
Yeah. A little.
我和我哥在一起
I'm here with my brother.
我之所以问这个  是因为女孩一个人在附近
Reason I asked is because it's not that safe around here
不太安全  你知道吗
for girls to be alone. You know?
-可能又吓着你了  对不起  -是  是  有一点
-Creepy. Once again. Sorry. -Yeah. Yeah. A little bit.
不知道为什么  这个镇吸引了不少
Just. For whatever reason. This town manages to attract
稀奇古怪的人
a lot of freaks and weirdoes.
当然我这人并不古怪
Not that I'm a freak or a weirdo.
看来我还是闭嘴好了  对吧
I'm just gonna stop talking. Okay?
好的
Okay.
想看些好东西吗  去弗洛格兄弟的店就对了
Wanna check something real? Check out the Frog Brothers' shop.
我想找个活干
I'm looking for some work.
这家店我打理的很好
I got the place pretty much handled.
是啊  我知道  看得出来
Yeah. I know. I can tell.
你看起来非常忙  我想找个做冲浪板的活
You seem really busy. But I was looking to shape.
这样的话  找弗洛格兄弟去吧
Well. In that case. Yeah. Check out Frog Brothers. Man.
他是附近唯一真正的冲浪板制造人
He's the only real shaper we have around here.
他的店在哪
Where's his shop at?
真不好说具体在什么地方  我给你画个地图
Man. It's in the ass-end of nowhere. But I'll draw you a map.
-我把电话号码给你  -这样就不怪异了
-I'm gonna give you my number. -Because that's not creepy.
-怪异吗  -我开玩笑的
-Is it? -I'm totally kidding.
好的  对不起
Okay. Sorry.
我都不知道你叫什么
I don't really even know your name.
-伊万  -我是妮可
-Evan. -I'm Nicole.
想找人出去玩的话给我打电话  给你
Just call me if you want somebody to hang out with. There you go.
酷
Cool.
应该就是这儿了
This should be it. Right up here.
真吸引人
Charming.
也许我疯了  可你觉得住在这儿的人
Call me crazy. But do you really think anyone who lives here
有能力花钱请你帮他们做冲浪板
would be able to pay you to shape?
试试也无妨啊
It doesn't hurt to try.
-好了  能走了吗  -不行  给我一张纸一支笔
-Okay. Can we go? -No. Hand me a piece of paper and a pen.
干嘛
Why?
万一他没电话  我想让他知道到什么地方可以找到我
Just in case he doesn't have a phone. I want him to know where to find me.
对啊  对啊  把咱们的地址贴在
Oh. Yes. Yes. Leave our address
德州电钮杀人狂的拖车上
at the creepy Texas Chainsaw Massacre trailer.
好主意
It's a good plan.
我还是觉得这儿比咱们的地方好
I still think it's nicer than our place.
你觉得淋浴器能用吗
And what do you think the state of the shower is?
不太可能
Not good.
我觉得还是试一下吧
I think I'm gonna give it a shot.
对不起  吓着你了
Sorry. Did I scare you?
不  抱歉  只是
No. Sorry. You just
我没听到你过来
I didn't hear you come up.
你想要幅画吗  可以存很久哦
You want a picture? It might last longer.
对不起  哥们  只是
Sorry. Man. Just
你和肖恩·帕沃斯非常像
You look exactly like Shane Powers.
说的对
That makes sense.
到底发生了什么  你拥有一切
What the hell happened to you. Man? You had everything.
你是世界上最好的冲浪手  为什么突然消失的无影无踪
You were the greatest surfer in the world and you just disappeared?
我也想问你同样的问题
I could probably ask you the same question.
是吧
Right?
是啊  我不知道
Yeah. Well. I don't know.
事情还没平静下来  我他妈也不知道发生了什么
The dust hasn't settled yet so I don't know what the hell happened.
最好快点搞清楚
Well. Don't take too long to figure it out.
有一个改变人生的机会  我抓住了它
But I had a chance to change my life and I took it. You know.
人生得意须尽欢
Carpe diem.
今晚有安排吗
You got plans for tonight?
没
No.
我要办个冲浪派对
I'm having a surf party.
你应该过来  见见其他人
You should cruise over. Meet the rest of the guys.
他们都很棒
They're killer.
我能去吗
Can I come?
不行  我觉得这不是个好主意
No. I don't think it's a good idea.
为什么不行
Why not?
不知道  感觉不好  我不知道
I don't know. A gut feeling I have. I don't know.
我刚认识这人
I just met this guy.
得了吧  高中时你墙上都是他的海报
Oh. Please. You had a poster of him on your wall in high school.
这就说明我该去他家  他
So I wanna go hang out at his house? He's
有点怪异
He's kind of a weirdo.
-怪异才好呢  -怪异就是怪异  知道吗
-Weird is good. -No. Weird is weird. All right?
-我不去  你就别作梦了  -你说不去是什么意思
-I'm not going. So just save your breath. -What do you mean you're not going?
克里斯  怎么  起来
Chris. What are? No. Get up. Okay?
-起来  今晚你应该出去玩玩  -不  我不去
-Get up. You need a night out. -No. I don't.
好  我今晚想出去玩
Okay. I need a night out.
走吧  起来
Let's go. Get up and
-嘿  -嗨
-Hey. -Hi.
不知道你俩今晚有事没  但
I don't know if the two of you are busy tonight or not. But
我租了"七宝奇谋"
I have got The Goonies.
你说啥
Excuse me?
"七宝奇谋"
The Goonies?
天哪  你们从没听说过"七宝奇谋"
Oh. My gosh. You mean to say the two of you have never heard of The Goonies?
这下可得好好补补了
You are in for a very serious treat.
事实上  我
Oh. Uh Actually. I mean. That
这个听起来很有意思  但我们今晚有事
Yeah. That sounds fun. But we actually have plans.
我们要去个派对
We're going to a party.
这挺好嘛
It's not gonna be that bad.
我先喝杯酒  再和你聊
Talk to me after I have a drink.
我马上将演示给你怎样做好一个
I'm about to show you how to make the badass
他妈的最变态的玛格丽塔酒配方
mother F.U.C.King sickest margarita recipe you've ever heard of.
你要拿100%纯度的蓝调龙舌兰酒
Take your hundred-percent,blue-agave tequila
一些新鲜的柠檬汁或果汁
a fresh squeeze of lemon and or lime juice
一些烈性的爽口酒  是那种...像那样的爽的
a little bit of an orange liqueur, something to kind of...take the edge off that.
第四个也是非常神秘的配方是
The fourth and very secret
把所有东西放进一个非常小的容器里
ingredient ties the whole room together.
就像把一个地毯放进一个豌豆里那样
Kind of like that rug in The Big Lebowski.
这不是他妈的克里斯·爱梅森和他
And it's Chris-fucking-Emerson and his
-火辣妹子妮可吗  -咱们走
hot piece-of-ass sister. Nicole? -Let's go.
-你们在这里干什么  -肖恩邀请我们的
-What are you guys doing here? -Shane invited us.
不  蠢货  这他妈是月亮湾
No. Idiot. Here in Luna Bay.
-你在跟踪我  -我们住在这儿
-Are you fucking stalking me? -We live here.
也许咱们俩可以再在一起  妮可
Maybe we can get together again. Nicole.
-你是他妈侍应生  新工作  -不是和你  是和你妹
-You bar-bitching? That your new job? -Not you. Maybe your hot sister. Though.
说到这儿  真是好久以前的事了
Speaking of which. It's been a long time.
-你穿着这个靴子很好看  -干嘛不闭上你那破嘴
-You're looking really good in those boots. -Why don't you stop being such an ass?
哦  对啦  滚吧
Ooh! Yeah. That's right. Walk away.
妮可  你真漂亮  越来越像熟女了
Nicole. You're looking good. You've really grown into yourself.
-滚蛋  -打电话给我
-Fuck off. -Call me.
我告诉你这不是个好主意
I told you this was a bad idea.
忘了他吧  他只是想接近你
Forget about him. He's trying to get to you.
我不管  我不想再在这待下去了
I don't care. I'm not staying at this party.
克里斯  这太蠢了  咱们才刚到
Chris. No. That's stupid. We just got here.
我哪也不想去  克里斯  我想在这好好玩玩  好吗
I don't wanna go anywhere. Chris. I wanna stay and have a good time. Okay?
我又不是孩子了
I'm not a kid anymore.
我知道不是了  但保护你是我的责任  咱们走吧
I know you're not. But you're still my responsibility. So let's go.
我不会惹麻烦的  好吧  我保证
Okay. I won't get in trouble. Okay? I promise.
我照顾好自己  你也照顾好自己  好吧
I'll take care of myself and you take care of yourself. Okay?
怎么了  哥们
Hey. Man. What's up? Yes. Dude.
哥们  太紧了  是吧
Dude. Right? That's tight. Bro.
现在先别看
Okay. Okay. Don't look now
但火盆边的小辣妹  正想方设法向你献媚呢
but that little hottie over there by the fire is giving you all kinds of love.
好好玩
Have fun.
嘿  妮可
Hey. Nicole.
妮可  妮可
Nicole. Nicole.
-哇  -你要干什么
-Whoo! Woo-hoo. -Hey. What's your deal?
你去那边  一个人坐那儿
The deal is you're gonna go over there and sit by yourself
一个人喝你的玛格丽特酒
and you're gonna drink these margaritas by yourself.
-不  不行  -强
-No. I'm not. -Jon.
别不识相  兄弟
Better than the alternative. Bro.
极至美景  是吗
It's a hell of a view. Isn't it?
是啊  这里整个地方  太让人难以置信了
Yeah. The whole place. It's incredible.
我一看到它  就立刻想占为己有
Yeah. When I saw that view. I just knew I had to have this place.
我是肖恩
I'm Shane.
我是妮可
I'm Nicole.
妮可  带你四处逛逛怎么样
Well. Nicole. How about I give you a little tour?
行啊
Yeah. Okay.
你是要过来呢  还是整晚都看我跳舞
So are you gonna make your move or are you just gonna watch me dance all night?
我在等属于我的一刻
I was waiting for my moment.
我觉得你的那一刻并不想管你  牛仔
Seems to me like your moment almost passed you by. Cowboy.
我不知道  你正站在这和我聊天
I don't know. You're standing here talking to me.
只是因为我对冲浪小子没有防御能力
Only because I have a weakness for surfer boys.
还因为我知道你是谁
And because I know who you are.
你喜欢冲浪
You follow surfing?
冲浪手
Surfers.
我喜欢冲浪手
I follow surfers.
有时候他们也喜欢我
And sometimes they follow me.
太他妈难以置信了
This is un-fucking-believable.
哇
Wow.
-这地方太棒了  -谢谢
-This place is amazing. -Thank you.
你和你哥在一起生活
So do you and your brother get along?
大部分时间吧
Yeah. Well. Most of the time. You know.
-不得不这样  -不得不  为什么
-Kind of have to. -You have to? Why's that?
因为我俩相依为命
Well. Because it's pretty much just us now.
几年前我们的父母死于车祸
Our parents died in a car accident a few years ago.
克里斯要远比我更难接受这一点
I think it was actually a lot harder on Chris than it was on me.
也许就是因为这个  他才失败了
You know. I think that's why he snapped.
因为这个他才在巡回赛被踢出局
Is that why he got kicked off the circuit?
-是啊  -原来如此
-Yeah. Yeah. -Yeah.
失去了所有赞助商  想起来就很不愉快
And lost all his sponsors. Not the right image.
我们越来越穷  所以来这儿了
So we started running out of money and that's how we ended up here.
是啊
Yeah. Yeah.
你哥是个好小伙  是吧
Well. Your brother's a good guy. Huh?
他只是遇到了挫折  你俩都是
He just got a tough break. You both did.
这个
Well
事实上我觉得死亡可以是件积极的事
I actually think death can be a positive thing.
因为
You know. Because
知道自己终将死去  能够让自己欣赏生活
knowing you're gonna die makes you appreciate life.
这就是所谓的及时行乐
The whole carpe diem thing.
年轻人有这样的观点很有意思
That's an interesting view for someone so young.
我没那么年轻
I'm not that young.
嗯
Well
死是生命的一部分
Dying is a part of living. You know?
我们每个人都会经历的  对吧
It's something that's gonna happen to all of us someday. Right?
那要看具体情况了
That depends.
我想做个实验
I wanna try something.
把这朵枯萎的玫瑰放在你手上
I want you to take this dead rose in your hand.
我相信  通过纯粹的意志力量
I believe that it's possible for us to change reality
我们有可能改变现实
through sheer force of will.
你觉得这可能吗
You think that's possible?
呃
Um
-我觉得会  -你觉得会还是你知道会
-I guess so. -You guess so or you know so?
-我知道  -你知道
-I know so. -You know so.
好的  闭上你的眼
Okay. Well. Then close your eyes.
闭上眼
Close your eyes.
注意力集中到玫瑰上
Now focus on this rose
想像一下它鲜活的时候是什么样子
and try to imagine what it must have been like when it was alive and vital.
感觉到了吗
Do you feel anything?
-当然  -嗯
-Definitely. -Mm-hm.
睁开眼
Open your eyes.
天哪
Oh. My God.
你怎么做到的
How did you do that?
魔力
Magic.
不是我做到的
And I didn't do it
我们做到的  我们一起
we did it. Together.
这是什么
What is it?
很不错  尝尝
It's good. Try it.
-闻起来不错  -嗯
-Smells good. -Mm-hm.
你觉得怎么样
What do you think?
我很喜欢
I like it.
-你还好吗  -是的
-You okay? -Yeah.
有点头晕
It just went right to my head.
出去呼吸点新鲜空气
You wanna go outside and get some fresh air?
好吗  咱们走
Yeah? Let's go.
想兜风去吗
You wanna go for a ride?
我不知道  外面有点冷
I don't know. It's kind of cold out.
哪它就派上用场了
Well. That's what this is for.
-嘿  强  强  -嘿
-Yo. Jon-Jon. -Hey.
看那个帅哥
Watch the pretty boy there.
咱们过去  让他开开眼
So here we are. Let's show him a little something.
-行  -现在走吧
-Yeah. -Come. Now.
-要不要和我上楼去  -你  卡尔
-Why don't you come upstairs with me -Yo. Kyle.
妈的  怎么了
What the fuck?
发生什么了  怎么了
What is it? What?
妈的  太他妈疼了  这可不好玩儿
Fuck. It fucking stings. Man. That's not cool.
你他妈混蛋  我正想把那妞搞上床呢
Fucking asshole. Man. I'm trying to get fucking laid.
这他妈还是件新衬衣  过来  过来
This is a fucking brand-new shirt. Prick. Come here. Come here.
过来  把他妈刀给我
Come here. Give me the fucking knife.
操你妈
What the fuck?
-过来  -他倒了
-Come back here. -Oh. Down he goes.
对不起
I'm sorry.
对不起  我得走了
I'm sorry. I gotta go.
我得去看看我妹妹
I have to go check on my sister.
-你妹妹  -对不起
Your sister? -Sorry.
你喜欢那样  我可以那么干
So you go that way. Huh? I can do that.
-对不起  我得走了  -等等  别走
-Sorry. I gotta go. -Wait. Don't leave.
-我得走了  -别走
-I gotta go. -Don't leave.
-真的  -别走  留下
-Come on. -Don't. Stay.
-对不起  -过来
-Sorry. -Come.
感觉好点了
Feel better?
-好多了  -真的
-Much. -Yeah?
我保证她现在很好  她和肖恩在一起
I'm sure she's fine. She's with Shane.
肖恩是个好人
You know. Shane's a good guy.
如果我是你  一定会为你妹与肖恩在一起高兴的
If I were you. I'd be happy that he's into your sister.
从摩托上下来
Hey. Get off the bike.
-干嘛  克里斯  -怎么了  伙计
-What? Chris. -What's up. Buddy?
-从摩托上下来  -有问题吗
-Get off the bike. -Is there a problem?
伙计  这是我和我妹妹之间的事
No. Dude. This is between me and my sister. Man. Thank you.
她能照顾好自己  伙计  相信我
She can handle herself. Man. Believe me.
-克里斯  -妈的
-Chris. -Oh. Hell. No.
-克里斯  -强
-Chris. -Jon.
-冷静点  -放他走
-Take it easy. -Let him go.
-冷静  -放手
-Calm down. -Get off of me.
-你保护过度了吧  -她是我家人  垃圾
-Overprotective much? -She's my family. Asshole.
冷静下来  混蛋  安静
Cool it. Bitch. Settle down.
-放他走  -什么
-Let him go. -What?
让他走
Let him go.
你他妈离我妹妹远点
Stay the hell away from my sister.
放手
Don't.
离"美宜堡"远点  混蛋
Stay the hell out of Malibu. Lebowski.
别像个玻璃一样走路
Stop walking like a fag.
我就知道咱们不应该去派对
-I knew we shouldn't have gone to that party.
我希望你做到两点  可你却完全无视
I asked you. Like. To do two things. And you completely ignore me.
别和不认识的男人出去玩儿
Do not hang out with some dude you don't know
别去那个男人的屋里
and don't go up to his room to party with the guy.
-好了  克里斯  我知道了  -怎么回事
-Okay. Chris. I get it. -What is that?
别说了
Stop it.
-应该告诉我你去了哪  -够了  别说了
-Should have told me where you were -That's enough. Stop it.
别表现的像是我爸似的
Stop trying to be my dad.
上帝啊
Oh. My God.
克里斯  我现在很不对劲
Chris. Something is seriously wrong with me right now.
你哪也没出问题  只不过喝多了
Nothing's wrong with you. You're just drunk.
克里斯  我没喝多
Chris. I am not drunk.
我特不对劲儿
Something is seriously the matter with me.
好  坚持一下  好吗  我们快到家了
Okay. Just hang on a little bit. All right? We're almost home.
天哪  我要
Oh. My God. Oh. My God. I'm gonna
我的胃
My stomach.
好了  你看  快到了
Look. All right. We're almost there.
我告诉你  我身体有了严重的问题
I'm telling you. There is something seriously the matter.
没事  你只需要喝一杯水和几片雅维
You're fine. You just need a glass of water and some Advil.
好了  你就是喝多了
All right. You're just drunk.
我没醉
I am not drunk.
-妮可  妮可  -我病了
-Nicole. Nicole. -I'm sick.
你是克里斯·爱梅森  我是埃德加·弗洛格
Chris Emerson? I'm Edgar Frog.
冲浪板制造者  吸血鬼猎手
Surfboard shaper and vampire hunter.
什么
What?
-嘿  别  -你在干什么
-Hey. Get -What are you doing?
听我说  你不知道自己在干什么
You don't know what you're doing.
我正设法救你们  你妹妹被感染了
I'm trying to save you. Your sister's infected.
-你在说什么  -她现在是不死之身了
-What are you talking about? -She's one of the undead.
从
Get
从我房子里滚出去
Get out of my house.
你会后悔的  朋友
It's your funeral. Pal.
我告诉你  从这滚出去
I told you to get the hell out of here. Man.
嗨
Hi.
咱们开始做的事还没结束
We didn't get to finish what we started.
是
Yeah.
不请我进去吗
Well. Aren't you gonna invite me in?
现在不是时候
Now's not the best time.
行
Yeah.
好了  请进
Okay. Come on in.
你知道吗  对不起  我不能这样
You know what? I'm sorry. I'm not
-我不能这样  我妹妹在后面  -我看能不能让你改变心意
-I can't do this with my sister back there. -Let me see if I can change your mind.
好吗
Yeah?
你味道真好
You taste good.
嘿
Oh. Hey.
丽莎  下来  停下
Lisa. Get off. Stop.
丽莎  停下
Lisa. Stop it.
真的  你有毛病吗
Seriously. Get What's the matter with you?
停下  真的  停下
Stop. Seriously. Stop.
从我身上下来
Get off me.
丽莎  下来
Lisa. Get off.
丽莎
Lisa?
哦  天哪
Oh. My God. Oh. My God.
妈的  怎么回事
What the fuck?
嘿  哥们
Hey. Man. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Hey. Whoa.
我直说了吧  我帮你摆脱那玩意
Let's get something straight. I let you get away with that shit
是因为我知道失去家人的感觉
because I understand what it's like to lose a family member to the other side.
如果它再出现一次  你得站在正确立场上  听懂了没
If it happens again. You're gonna end up on the wrong side of the stake. Are we clear?
-嗯  -好
-Mm-hm. -Good.
听着  我只是
It's cool. Man. Look. I just
我不知道怎么回事  明白吗
I don't understand what's going on. All right?
你说我妹妹被感染了
You said my sister was infected?
你妹妹成了不死族的一员
Your sister's become a member of the undead.
夜晚出没  吸人鲜血
A night stalker. A bloodsucker.
就像诺斯·费拉图
Nosferatu.
你妹妹成了吸血僵尸
Your sister's a suck monkey.
哥们  这太荒谬了
Dude. That's That's ridiculous. Man.
荒谬  那你现在为什么来这里
Ridiculous? Then what are you doing here?
你离开我  我家发生了非常怪异的事
Look. Some crazy shit happened at my place after you left.
什么"怪异的事"
Define "crazy shit."
一个小妞来我家
Well. This This chick came into my house and
她长出獠牙  变成石头  最后爆炸了
And she sprouted fangs and then she turned into stone and exploded.
这才叫荒谬
Now. That's just ridiculous.
吸血鬼是不会石化然后爆炸的
Vampires don't just turn into stone and then explode.
想让它们死必须用利器刺穿心脏
They have to be pierced through the heart with a sharp object.
我想鹿角也许起了这个作用
You know. I guess the antlers could have done that.
我原以为它可能是木制的
I thought it had to be a wooden stake or something.
这就是神秘之处  任何利器都可以
That's a myth. Any sharp object will do.
事实上  它并不用很锋利
As a matter of fact. It doesn't have to be sharp.
钝器也可以  只要刺穿心脏就行
It can be a blunt object. As long as it pierces the heart.
我说我妹妹也成为它们中的一员
You said my sister was one of them?
-怎么会这样  -有两种可能
-But how would that happen? -One of two ways:
首先  她可能被咬了
Either A. She was bit
或者她喝了吸血鬼首领的血
or B. She drank the blood of the head vampire.
你怎么会这么了解吸血鬼
How do you know so much about vampires?
漫画  我的朋友  我是从漫画中学的
Comic books. My friend. Comic books.
我向你寻求解答  你却告诉我你是从漫画里学的
I ask you for answers and you give me comic books?
看漫画能学到好多有用的东西
A lot of valuable information can be gained by reading comic books.
比如
For example
看到了没
see here?
这个可怜的笨蛋  正在喝吸血鬼首领的血
This poor sap's drinking the blood of the head vampire.
它们把血放在酒杯当中骗人喝下去
They like to trick people by putting it into wine bottles.
朋友  你喝的是什么
Dude. What are you drinking. Man?
弗洛格汁
Frog Juice.
大蒜  圣水和生鸡蛋
Garlic. Holy water and raw eggs.
好  你认为  根据漫画所说
Okay. So what you're saying is. Based on a comic book
我妹妹喝了血  成了吸血鬼
my sister drank blood and now she's a vampire.
半  她是半吸血鬼
Half. She's only half vampire.
杀人以后  她才会变成完全的吸血鬼
She won't make the transition to full bloodsucker until she makes her first kill.
-好吧  -事实上  这的确很好
-Great. -That is great. Actually.
这意味着还有时间挽救她人类的灵魂
Because it means you still have time to save her mortal soul.
你需要做的就是  在她吸血之前  杀掉吸血鬼首领
All you have to do is kill the head vampire before she feeds.
有人么
Hello?
门开着
It's open.
嗨
Hi.
我带了酒
I brought wine.
我喜欢酒
I love wine.
老实说  我真没想到你有那么喜欢我
To be honest. I really didn't think you dug me all that much.
-为什么这么想  -只是一种感觉而已
-Why would you think that? -Just a vibe I got. I guess.
现在有什么样感觉
What vibe are you getting now?
太棒了
A really good one.
-妮可  -妈的
-Nicole. -Oh. Shit.
你  你做了她么
Did? Did you do it?
-滚出去  -我们什么都没干
-Get the hell out of here. -We didn't do anything. Man.
我不知道你俩是天主教徒还是什么
Dude. I didn't know you guys were born-again Christians or whatever.
我没有和你妹妹发生关系
Man. I'm not using your sister.
-嗯  很高兴听到这个  谢谢  -我真的喜欢她
-Yeah. Good to know. Thank you. -I really like her.
我有一个好消息  也有一个坏消息
-This is basically one of those. Like. Good news bad news scenario things.
你先听哪个
What do you want first?
妈的  先听坏消息吧
Oh. Shit. Okay. The bad news.
好  坏消息是那天肖恩给你的酒
Okay. The bad news is that the wine that Shane gave you the other night
实际是并不是酒  而是血
wasn't wine. All right. It was blood.
肖恩的血
Shane's blood.
好
Right.
好了  克里斯  我知道你不喜欢这人
Okay. Chris. I know you don't like the guy.
但是  这也太恶心了
But. Like. That's disgusting.
不  因为喝了他的血  你变成了吸血鬼
No. And by drinking his blood. You've been turned into a vampire.
对  我是吸血鬼  克里斯  太好了
Right. I'm a vampire. Chris. Great.
别这么招人讨厌  我不是吸血鬼
Stop being such an asshole. I'm not a freaking vampire.
我不是招人讨厌
I'm not being an asshole. Nicole.
我知道这听起来很荒谬  但是你看
I know it sounds ridiculous. But take a look.
什么东西消失了
See anything missing?
你
You.
不  是吸血鬼  你不是想和那人发生关系
No. Vampire. You weren't gonna make out with that kid
而是想吃他
you were gonna eat him.
你长了獠牙  眼神很疯狂  我全看见了
You had fangs and crazy eyes. I saw it all.
好吧  好消息最好确实非常好
Okay. The good news better be really fucking good.
好消息简直是棒极了  知道吗
No. The good news is great news. Okay?
听着  现在你只是半吸血鬼
See. Right now you're only. Like. Half of a vampire.
意味着你可以变回人类
Which means you can be turned back human.
只要艾迪和我在你吃人之前  杀掉吸血鬼首领
As long as Eddie and I kill the head vampire before you feed.
-所以谁也不要吃  -什么  谁是艾迪
-So just don't eat anyone. -What? Who's Eddie?
艾迪·弗洛格  他是个吸血鬼杀手
Eddie Frog. He's a vampire slayer.
-我以为他是个做冲浪板的  -呃  他也是
-I thought he was a surfboard shaper. -Well. That too.
对  好的
Right. Okay.
咱们把事情说清楚  你要和
Let me just get this straight then. So you've teamed up
一个冲浪制造板以及  吸血鬼杀手联合起来
with a surfboard-shaper-slash-vampire-hunter
去杀我非常喜欢的那个人
so you can kill this guy who I'm totally crushing on
从而把我从永远的天谴中解救出来
so you can save me from eternal damnation?
-差不多就这样  -对  差不多就是这样
-Is that pretty much it? -Yeah. That's pretty much it.
-不  冷静  冷静  -不  克里斯  我不会冷静的
-No. Calm down. Calm down. -No. Chris. I'm not gonna calm down.
-不  -你怎么了
-No. -What's wrong with you?
我想吃那个人  你意识到了吗
I tried to eat that guy. Do you realize that?
你知道我有多么想喝人血吗
Do you know what it's like for me to want to drink blood?
你知道这有多恶心吗  我是个素食主义者
Do you know how disgusting that is? I'm a vegetarian.
他藏在1号门后
Is he behind Door Number 1?
2号门
Door Number 2?
或者是
Or Door Number
3号门
咱们遇到麻烦了
We're screwed.
有许多地方  都可能是他们的老巢
There's just too many places where the nest could be.
我已经告诉你肖恩是吸血鬼头目
Look. I already told you. Shane's the head vampire.
我们几天前在他家参加过一次派对
We went to party at his house a couple nights ago.
那里一定就是老巢
It's gotta be the nest.
自重的吸血鬼
There's no way that any self-respecting vampire
绝对不会住在像那样的地方
would ever live in a place like that.
我的意思是
I mean.
它们也许把那个地方当作陷阱  也许在那里吃人
They may use it as a lure or a place to feed
但它们绝对不会在那里睡觉
but they'd never sleep there.
吸血鬼
Vampires
总会找人类遭受过苦难的地方
always look for a place with a history of human suffering.
幽深  黑暗  阴冷的地方
Deep, dark, dank places.
不见天日的地方
Places that never see the light of day.
爬满寄生虫的地方
Places with lots of vermin.
充满腐烂泥土气息的地方
Places that smell of rot and earth
和老化的
and decay.
妮可
Nicole.
快点
Hurry.
我们不可能找到老巢在哪里
There's no way we can find out where the nest is
除非打入它们内部
without you being in their inner circle.
好  那我去
Well. Then that's what I'll do.
把他们带出来
I'll get back in with them.
-我要先成为它们的一员  -别这么蠢  行吗
-I'm gonna become one of them. -Don't be stupid. All right?
他们能在你之前阅读你的思想
They can read your thoughts before you have them.
得了吧  她是我的家人  混蛋
Come on. Man. She's family. Asshole.
你感情用事了
You hit a soft spot there.
我知道失去兄弟姐妹的滋味
I know what it's like to lose a sibling.
如果你要打入内部  就得一直在内部待下去
If you're gonna do this. Then you have to do it all the way.
我的意思是  你首先得受它诱使堕落
I mean. You have to be seduced by it.
屈从于它
You have to succumb to it.
你得一直在他们内部  直到快要完全变成吸血鬼
You have to take it all the way to the brink of becoming a full vampire.
然后在最后关头  再背叛他们
And then you have to betray them at the last possible moment.
你觉得你能做到吗
Do you think you can really handle that?
只能这么干了  艾迪
It's the only way. Eddie.
埃德加
Edgar.
对不起  埃德加
Sorry. Edgar.
你知道我是对的
You know I'm right.
这是一场危险的游戏
It's a dangerous game.
一场极有可能输的游戏
And it's one that you're likely to lose.
一定要知道
So just know
如果你忘记了自己的立场
if you forget your place
你也成了吸血鬼
and you become one of them
我也会杀你
l'll be coming for you.
这玩意真酷
This shit's cool.
卡尔  别他妈自己玩了  游戏要开始了
-Yo. Kyle. Stop playing with yourself. Man. The game gonna start.
-妈的骗我  -你知道吗
-Fucking cheater. -You know what?
-我叫你了  布雷森  -你没有
-I been calling you. Brethren. -You haven't been calling me.
闭嘴
Shut up.
总打得你屁滚尿流
Always with your crying.
-快退游戏  居然骗我  -听着  别哭
-Dude. Quit it. Fucking cheater. -Listen. Don't start crying.
你看  你看
Check it out. Check it out.
录下来
Tape them.
-快录下来  -想溜
-Tape them. Man. -Skin out.
-好辣啊  -看她的屁股
-So nice. -Backside.
-对头  你个混蛋  -妈的
-Yeah. Bitch. -Holy fuck.
-你他妈有病啊  -操你妈
-What the fuck is your problem? -Motherfucker.
-你死定了  -你打我啊  呵呵
-You're a dead man. -Yeah. Fucking blow me. Buddy. Again.
-这下轮到谁骗谁了  -白人垃圾
-Who's the cheater now? -Fucking white people.
把它拉出来  没心情和你玩
Pull this out. I ain't playing.
-这个视频会在网上传得到处都是  -闭嘴  滚蛋
-You're gonna be all over the fucking Net. -Stop. Fuck off.
你的血喷得到处都是
Dude. You're fucking squirting everywhere.
-你是个喷壶  -肖恩
-You're a squirter. -Shane.
我哥怎么办
What about my brother?
我不想失去他
I don't wanna lose him.
你不会的
You won't.
相信我
Trust me.
全名
Full name?
呃  妮可
Uh. Nicole.
爱
Em
爱梅森
Emerson.
好的  我们会联系你的
All right. We'll call you.
这就完了  把她的名字输到电脑里
That's it? Just gonna type her name onto a computer
寄希望于别人像小狗一样把她交回来
and hope someone turns her in like a dog pound?
-怎么这么被动  -孩子  我们有失踪系统
-Isn't that kind of passive? -Son. We have a system.
长官  你们肯定能做些什么
Officer. There's gotta be something you can do
-警长  -警长  对不起
-Sheriff. -Sheriff. I'm sorry.
我真的非常担心她
I'm really worried about her.
在周边地区有许多失踪了
We have a lot of missing persons around here.
我知道  但如果他们不是失踪呢
I know. I mean. What if they're not missing. You know?
还有其他可能
It could be something else.
孩子  走吧  我们有失踪系统
Son. Hit the road. We have a system.
月亮湾  麦克格雷警长
Luna Bay. Sheriff McGraw.
真的  多大
Really? How big?
上周我钓到25磅重的一条
Yeah. Last week I caught about a 25-pounder.
没什么用  是吧
Not very helpful. Huh?
我想问问他们能不能帮忙寻找丽莎
Yeah. I was gonna ask them if they could help us find Lisa.
好几天没见她了
Haven't seen her in a couple of days.
上次我不是还见你和她在一起吗
Hey. Didn't I see you with her last?
我妹妹在哪儿
Where's my sister. Man?
对了  你妹妹
Oh. Yeah. Your sister.
大概一小时前我见过她
Man. I saw her like an hour ago.
看起来她度过一段非常美妙的时光
She looked like she was having a really good time.
我妹妹到底他妈的在哪儿
Where the hell is my sister. Man?
放松点  小男人  好吗
Oh. Hey. Hey. Relax. Little man. Okay?
我告诉你  你最好冷静一点
Trust me when I tell you this is. Right here. A time that you wanna keep your cool
如果你还想见到妮可的话
if you ever wanna see Nicole again.
你想要什么
What do you want?
不是我想要什么  兄弟
It's not what I want. Bro
而是肖恩想要什么
it's what Shane wants.
上车
Get in the car.
怎么样  女士们
How's it. Ladies?
吸血鬼杀手先生  过得好吗
Mr. Vampire Slayer. How you doing?
你还好吗
You okay?
我很好
I'm good.
非常好
I'm really good.
昨晚很抱歉
Sorry about last night. Man.
你在保护自己的妹妹
You were protecting your sister.
我知道
I get it.
但我从来没有伤害过她
But I'd never do anything to hurt her.
事实上  如果你进一步了解一下
In fact. Once you understand it a little more.
你会发现我送给了妮可一份礼物
You'll see I've given Nicole a gift.
你知道对死亡的恐惧  多么限制你吗  克里斯
Do you know how much the fear of death has limited you. Chris?
它对你的一生有多大的消极作用
The negative impact it's had on your life?
你可能都没考虑过这些
You're probably not even aware of it.
我不是只在谈你自己对死亡的恐惧
And I'm not just talking about the fear of your own death. No.
看看失去亲人的恐惧  对你造成了多大的影响
Look at what the fear of losing your loved ones has done to you.
你这么担心失去妮可
You've been so worried about losing Nicole
以致于变得歇斯底里  有过度保护倾向
that it's made you paranoid and overprotective.
我能带走这份恐惧
I can take that fear away.
我能让你成为家庭的真正一部分  克里斯
I can make you part of a real family. Chris.
永远不会消亡的家庭
One that never dies.
卡尔的家庭很久以前就把他注销掉了
Kyle's human family wrote him off a long time ago.
他们以为他死于自杀
They thought he was suicidal.
但我看见了真实的他
But I saw him for what he truly was
一个对肾上腺素上瘾的人
an adrenaline junkie.
艾瑞克  他的过去我们说的越少越好
Erik. Well. The less we say about his past. The better.
我们不想让你成为犯罪后的从犯  对吧
We wouldn't wanna make you an accessory after the fact. Now would we?
小强尼
And Jonny boy. Well
你打碎他的膝盖后  他原以为再也不能冲浪了
after you shattered his knee. He was never supposed to surf again.
看看他现在
Look at him now.
比以往任何时候都强壮  兄弟
Stronger than ever. Bro.
要想真正了解我们是什么  克里斯
But for you to truly understand what we are. Chris
你必须用我们的方式来理解世界
you have to see the world the way we do.
你和你妹妹
You and your sister
永远不会变老
will never grow old
永远不会死  再也不知道恐惧是什么
you'll never die and you'll never know fear again.
但首先你得先拿着这个
But you have to take that first step.
要干什么
And what's that?
我和男孩们想出来的一点小乐子
It's a little something me and the boys came up with.
勇士们
Warriors.
-怎么  -出来玩玩
-What the? -Come out to play.
咱们走
Let's go.
哦  妈的
Oh. Shit.
走  走
Now! Now!
抓紧
Yo. Hold up.
让他出来  卡尔
Let him out. Kyle.
喜欢吗  婊子
How do you like that. Bitch?
走  走
Go. Go.
跳  克里斯
Jump it. Chris.
妈的
Fuck you!
-妈的  -是啊
-Fuck you. -Yeah.
滚蛋
Fuck you!
喜欢吗
How do you like that?
无与伦比
Hey. On top of the world. Ma.
等等  兄弟
Hold on. Brother.
这是家私人俱乐部  你还不是会员
It's a private club and you're not a member.
的确  还不是
Not yet. Anyway.
如果我说愿意加入呢
Well. What if I say yes?
仔细考虑一下  克里斯
Think long and hard about it. Chris.
一旦加入我们  就没回头路了
Once you join the tribe. There's no turning back.
你的支票被退回了
Your check bounced.
不  只是  我把钱转移下帐户
No. It's I transferred some money from one account to the other. So
别费话了  我要你马上给我新的押金
Save the bull for your buddies. I'm gonna need a new security deposit immediately.
必须是现金支票或是汇票
It's gonna need to be in the form of a cashier's check or a money order.
也许是我的错  给了你们一个错误印象
Maybe this is my fault. Maybe I gave the wrong impression.
好了  不是什么大事  再等两天好吗
Come on. It's not that big of a deal. Just wait two days.
让我说完  摘掉太阳镜好吗
Just let me finish. Could you please take your sunglasses off?
不看着你的眼睛  我没法和你说话
I can't talk to you unless I can see your eyes.
听着  我不想让你们觉得我想插手
Look. I didn't want you guys to feel like I was trying to step in
扮演你们父母的角色  但你们玩得也太疯了吧
and act like your parents. But that doesn't mean you can go crazy here.
我看见你妹妹和一个男人上床  她才多大
I saw your sister had a guy over last night. How old is she?
-差不多快18了  -那就是说她今年才17
-She's almost. Like. 18. -That means she's 17 years old.
你整天整晚的出出进进
And you coming and going at all hours of the day and night
我仔细想过
You know. I have a reputation to think of. L
虽然我不是你们的妈妈
I realize I am not your mother. But
但你们  不能在我的地盘上为所欲为
But you Doesn't mean you can behave like this on my property.
好的  对不起
All right. I'm sorry.
是啊  我也一样
Yeah. Me too.
晚上派对  白天睡觉
Partying all night. Sleeping all day.
你们不能像吸血鬼一样活着
You both need to quit acting like a couple of vampires.
太荒谬了
This is ridiculous.
你和你妹妹
You and your sister
永远不会变老
will never grow old
永远不会死  再也不知道恐惧是什么
you'll never die and you'll never know fear again.
你吸得太多了  太多了
-You're sharking it. Man. You're sharking it.
谁想吸点
Who wants some?
现在你知道问了
Now you ask?
-我们去哪  -恶魔礁
-Where we headed? -Devil's Reef.
听说现在有篝火派对
I hear it's firing right now.
-今晚在那冲浪  -对啊  为什么不
-We're paddling out tonight? -Yeah. Why not?
没有月亮  估计我们什么都看不到
-There's no moon. Bet we're not gonna see anything.
怎么  你们有夜视眼之类的吗
What. You guys have night vision or something?
你说的是什么样的夜视眼  小子
-What kind of night vision you chatting about. Boy?
-变得像蝙蝠一样  -电影看太多了  兄弟
-Can't you turn yourselves into bats? -Way too many movies. Bro.
我们没有夜视眼  克里斯
Yeah. We don't have night vision. Chris.
蝙蝠也没有夜视眼  它们有声纳
Bats. They don't actually have night vision either. They have sonar.
你知道吗  克里斯  你对了一半
You know what? You're half right.
我之前告诉过你  我们看东西的方法与人不一样
Like I told you before. We do see things differently.
尝尝这个以后
Kind of like you're about to.
你也就知道了
After you have a little taste of this.
再见  小子
Bye. Boy.
你还什么都没看到  克里斯
-You haven't seen anything yet. Chris.
不会看到什么的  转变还没结束
-No. You ain't. You're not done yet.
等着看我们约的女孩在礁石上等我们吧  兄弟
Wait till you see the girls we got waiting for us at the reef. Bro.
一定会很疯狂的  兄弟
It's gonna be crazy. Bro.
疯狂
Crazy.
好了  轮到我了
All right. My turn.
你知不知道少管别人闲事
-Did you ever hear of getting your own thing?
你知不知道闭上你那破嘴
Did you ever hear of shutting the hell up?
管好你自己吧  让开
You mind yourself. Boy. Mister. Ease off.
好了  够了
All right. Enough.
怎么了
What? What. What?
麻烦给我摄像机
Camera. Please.
好了  女孩们
All right. Girls.
我打赌你们彼此不敢接吻
I dare you guys to kiss.
给我看些我在youtube上看不到的东西
Show me something that I can't find on YouTube.
那人是你啊
That's you.
很好  继续继续
Nice.Go, go, go.
那个是什么  那个就是我正在说的
What's that? That's what I'm talking about.
宝贝你有什么给我们看的
What about you, sweet thing?
-你们真的想让她那样做  -不
-You gonna let her step you up like that? -No.
让我们看看她给我们带来什么  你给我带来什么
What has she got? What do you got for me?
啊哈
Oh,SHE
很好  很性感  但是这些东西始终...
Oh, yes. That's sexy, but still that's something I could see...
...在我和我女朋友幽会的时候可以看到  所以...
...on my Girls Gone Wild box set, so...
-真的不信  -真的
-Double dare? -Double dare.
妈的  看见了吗  真的  快看
-Oh. Fuck. Are you seeing this? Seriously. Watch.
我想她们敢
I think so.
-伙计们  -哦  嘿
-Guys? -Oh. Hey.
-我们要走了  -你们去哪儿
-We're out of here. -Where are you going?
回我们的地方
Back to our place
-喝一杯  -我和你们一起回去
for a drink. -I'll come with you.
不  留下  克里斯  你还有好多事要干
-No. Hang back. Chris. There's plenty for you to do here.
另外  这是妮可的时刻
Besides. This is Nicole's time.
坐下吧  哥们
Just have a seat. Man.
好样的
Attaboy.
看看这个
So check this out.
你知道盐水和血基本上是一种东西吗
Do you know that salt water and blood are basically the same thing?
真的
It's true.
法国生物学家在狗身上做了实验
There's a French biologist that did this experiment on a stray dog
大概是在世纪之交的时候
around the turn of the century.
他放干了狗的血  并用盐水替代
He drained all the blood out of the dog and replaced it with diluted seawater
所有人都以为狗死定了
and everybody thought that this dog was gonna die.
但它没有
Except the dog didn't.
失去的血再生了
What they found is that all the missing blood had regenerated.
盐水变成了血
The saltwater became blood.
此后  这条狗比以前更加活跃  精力旺盛
And after that. The dog was more alive and vibrant than it ever had been before.
这条狗很健康地活了很久
The dog went on to live a long and very healthy life.
敬长寿  克里斯
To long life. Chris.
我也试试这个
Let me try some of that.
我觉得你肯定不会喜欢的
-I don't really think you'd find it too much to your liking.
还是喝你的啤酒吧
You might wanna just stick with the beer.
你这个又长又无聊的故事想说明什么
So what exactly was the point of your very long and boring story. Jon?
基本上  他想说的就是
Basically. What he's trying to say is
我们是吸血鬼
we're vampires.
-好可怕  -不  但事实上
-Ooh. Scary. -No. But seriously
我们就是吸血鬼
we're vampires.
救命
Help me!
不  不  不
No. No. No.
不要  求求你
No. Please.
放我走吧
Let me go.
闭上你的臭嘴
Shut the fuck up.
不  不  不
No. No. No.
我太喜欢这女孩了  妈的  太喜欢了
I'm thinking I love this girl. Oh. Fuck. I love this girl.
吃啊
Do it.
Do it!
跑啊  快点
Run. Go.
快点
Come on.
你完蛋了  兄弟
You're fucked up. Bro.
肖恩不会在这救你  我受够你了
Shane's not around to save your ass and I've had it with your attitude.
你以为我是在开玩笑么
Guess you think I'm kidding you. Bud
但我没开玩笑
but it ain't so.
肖恩现在在哪儿  混蛋
Where's Shane now. Bi? Fuck.
现在没棍子了  是吧
You ain't got no fucking stick now. Do you?
快点  结束这一切吧
Come on. Let's finish this.
嘿
Hey!
谁订了十字架
Who ordered the stake?
你能控制住自己吗
Are you cool?
是的  我能
Yeah. I'm cool.
你能吗
I said. Are you cool?
让我看看你的牙
Show me your teeth.
我说了  我能
I said I'm cool.
我说了  让我看看你的牙
And I said. Show me your teeth.
我能控制住
I am cool.
没错  看得出来
Yeah. I can see that.
没时间纠缠这些破事了  艾迪
We don't have time for this shit. Eddie.
咱们得赶回老巢  在我妹妹吸血之前救她出来
We have to get to the nest and get my sister before she feeds.
我也正想这么说
That's what I'm talking about.
我讨厌他妈的吸血鬼
I hate fucking vampires.
你在干什么
What are you doing. Man?
变圣水
Turning this into holy water.
-我是牧师  -你是牧师
-I'm a minister. -You're a minister?
对  我是在网上被任命的
Yup. I got ordained online.
我被国际在线牧师协会认证
I'm officially recognized by the International Association of Online Ministers
为尊敬的埃德加·弗洛格牧师  吸血鬼猎人
as the Honorable Reverend Edgar Frog. The vampire hunter.
你受过训练
Did you study for that?
没有  我在网上填了几张表
No. I went to the website. Filled out a couple forms
然后点击了"任命我"
and clicked "Ordain Me."
在战斗开始前  有几件事你得知道
Now. Before going into battle. There's a few things that you need to be briefed on.
首先  吸血鬼死的样子不好看
First of all. When a vampire buys it. It's never a pretty sight.
没有死法一样的吸血鬼
No two bloodsuckers go out the same way.
有些大喊大叫  有些一声不吭  有些爆炸  有些内爆
Some yell and scream. Some go quietly. Some explode. Some implode
但他们全想拉你垫背
but all will try to take you with them.
至于猎鬼武器
As far as your arsenal of vamp artillery:
我们有十字架
We got stakes.
有木头的  有金属的
Got some wooden ones. Got some metal ones
还有碳纤维的
and some carbon-fibers.
我喜欢树脂的  又轻又好用
I like the resins. They're light and easy to handle.
老东西就是好  经典木制
That said. There's nothing as good as the old-fashioned. Classic wood job.
安全  结实  可靠
Safe. Sturdy. Reliable.
我们有空气推动榴弹发射器  用以发射圣水球
Next. We have my air-propelled-rocket grenade launcher for holy-water balloons.
这是我的玩意  你别碰它
This is my baby. Don't touch it.
我们还有一个这东西
We also have one of these.
-你知道怎么用吧  -是的  当然
-You know how to use this. Right? -Yeah. Totally.
-好的  -不  伙计  我不知道这是什么
-Okay. Good. -No. Dude. I have no idea what that is.
这是大蒜腊肠
It's a garlic bolo.
别管了  还是我拿这个吧
Never mind. I'll hold on to this one.
咱们去杀几个吸血鬼
Let's go kill some vampires.
他们知道我们在这
They know we're here.
准备好了吗
Are you ready?
-我想是的  -你想是的
-I guess so. -You guess so?
我确定
I know so.
救救我
Help me.
闻到了吗
You smell that?
真菌与死亡的气息
Smells like fungus or death.
吸血鬼的味道
It's vampire BO.
什么
What?
-你到底在说什么  -跟着我就行了
-What the hell are you talking about? -Just follow me.
妮可  救救我
Nicole. Help me.
伊万
Evan.
我不能
I can't.
但你说已经准备好了
You said you were ready.
但我认识他
But I know him.
他是横亘在我们之间唯一的障碍  妮可
Well. He's the only thing that still stands between us. Nicole.
横亘在你与不朽之间的唯一障碍
The only thing that stands between you and immortality.
如果你想和我在一起
If you wanna be with me
如果你爱我
if you love me
就吸了他的血
you'll do this.
安静  你会惊醒死人了
Quiet. Man. You'll wake the dead.
克里斯
Chris.
妈的
Shit.
说好一起行动的  怎么不听呢
What part of "stay together" don't you understand?
有不对劲的味道
I smell ugly.
克里斯
Chris.
出来  克里斯
Come on. Chris.
克里斯不在这儿  艾迪
Chris isn't here. Eddie
你弟弟在
but your brother is.
你在哪
Where are you?
的确恶心
Yup. It's ugly.
失手
Missed.
狐狸逃不过好猎手
Pop goes the weasel.
克里斯
Chris.
永远在一起
Stay forever.
长生不老
Live forever.
与家人相伴
Stay with family.
克里斯
Chris.
欢迎
Welcome.
克里斯
Chris.
像你这样的人我等了很久  克里斯
I've been waiting to meet someone like you for quite some time. Chris.
厉害人物  能够挑战我的人
Someone that would push the boundaries. Someone that would challenge me.
-我觉得你可以  -克里斯
-I saw that in you. -Chris.
我不想失去你
I don't wanna lose my brother.
来吧  吸取一个人的精华
Come on. Taking in someone's essence
饮用他的鲜血
consuming living human blood
这才是真正的乐趣
that's the real rush.
不
No!
肖恩
Shane!
不  肖恩  住手
No. Shane. Stop.
你快杀了他了  肖恩
You're killing him. Shane!
不
No!
妮可
Nicole.
为什么
Why?
他是我的家人  混蛋
He's family. Asshole.
肖恩
Shane.
肖恩  住手
Shane. Stop.
妮可
Nicole.
为人搭一个火堆
Build a man a fire
他可以温暖一天
and he's warm for a day.
告诉他如果生火
Light a man on fire
能温暖他一生
and he's warm for the rest of his life.
你们得为我的服务付款
You'll be getting a bill for my services.
-谢谢  艾迪  -我就是干这个的
-Thanks. Eddie. -Hey. It's what I do.
另外我叫埃德加
And it's Edgar.
我能否
Hey. Is it?
我能否找时间约你出来
Is it cool if I call you sometime?
呃
Uh
好的
Okay.
太棒了
Yes!
哇哦
Woo-hoo!
完全不能接受
This is completely unacceptable.
我知道你们干了些什么
I know exactly what you've been up to.
我告诉你们  一切必须停止
I am telling you. It has to stop right now.
我不会袖手旁观  任由我关心的两个年轻人
I will not stand by and watch two young people that I care about
掉入这样的深渊  听明白了吗
fall into this trap. You hear me?
如果我再发现一点苗头
So if I so much as see one seed
或者闻到有大麻味
or catch one whiff of reefer
相信我  我知道大麻的味道是什么
And believe me. I know what it smells like.
我就叫警察了
-I'm calling the cops.
绝不是警告  我实施零容忍政策  知道了没
No warning. We are talking zero tolerance. You got that?
谈话结束
End of discussion.
快现身吧
Cut the theatrics.
我知道你就在那儿
I know you're out there.
现身吧
Show yourself.
被十字架刺中不失为一种好归宿  萨姆
That's a good way to get yourself staked. Sam.
放松  朋友
Easy there. Compadre.
在你干了那些蠢事之后
After all the shit that you pulled?
我觉得你至少应该听我把话说完  你欠我的
I think you can at least hear me out. I mean. I feel like you owe me that.
你以为我能表现得  就像什么都没发生过
You really expect me to act like nothing ever happened?
不  我已经原谅了你
No. I've already forgiven you.
这是无法改变的事实
It's water under the bridge.
待在那儿
Stay there.
-你不会希望像这样完蛋的  -你才会完蛋
-You don't want it to go down like this. -Oh. It's going down like this.
我警告你
I'm warning you.
吓死我了
Hey. I'm trembling.